Hi!
We're making light switch plate covers.
We already have all the Mod Podge we need.
One thing you need to remember is when it dries, that's how it's going to stay.
You can tell I did even strokes.
They're all nice and in one direction.
It can dry like that.
I don't have any fingerprints on there.
It's going to dry like that.
It needs to dry completely before you put glitter on it if you want to.
I'm going to put mine on this one today.
The thing is we need it to dry.
Don't let anyone touch it.
Don't let it fall and get lint on it from your carpet.
Let's pick it up.
Don't touch it because your fingerprint will be on there.
We're going to set it somewhere.
If you want to dry it, you can put a fan on it.
Doesn't take long to dry.
It's just like Elmer's glue.
Let it sit somewhere and let it dry completely.
Make sure it's the way you want it and it's shaped the way you want it.
Once it dries, it's done.